# PATRYK PIETRZYK

# JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER



+48 729 923 232 patryk.pietrzyk@op.pl

Poland, Silesian 43-300 Bielsko-Biała

## **SUMMARY**

I am a beginner web developer with constantly growing experience.

My dream is to become a full time front-end developer and change the hobby into actual work.

For now on I trying my best at knowing better JavaScript and at the nearest future I want to learn React.js and Node.js

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML5 / CSS3
- SASS
- Bootstrap 5
- JavaScript
- GIT
- Writing DRY & CLEAN code in responsive style
- Ability to work in team and under pressure
- Complex problem solving & creative thinking

## **LINKS**

- GitHub: https://github.com/Skaxx
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/patrykpietrzyk/
- Portfolio: https://patryk-pietrzyk.pl/indexENG.html
- Commercial project: https://andytrans.pl/

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Escort/Pilot driver**

ANDYTRANS - Andrzej Paluchowski · Opole 02/2022 - present

Piloting oversize vehicles in Poland and Europe.

#### **Escort/Pilot driver**

Transport Międzynarodowy Ireneusz Strychacz · Jemielnica 03/2021 - 12/2021

Piloting oversize vehicles in Poland and Europe.

#### **Insurance and Finance Specialist**

Aegon · Bielsko-Biała 04/2020 - 11/2020

Active customer acquisition and professional customer service.

My work has been based on sale:

- Different insurance products
- Investment and saving products
- Planning the client's finances according to his needs

## **Bank representative - Private banking**

ING Bank Śląski · Bielsko-Biała 07/2019 - 01/2020

Active customer acquisition and professional customer service. Sale of banking products for private and business clients.

All the above-mentioned duties were performed with due diligence.

### **Business owner**

CleanUp - Patryk Pietrzyk · Górki Wielkie 07/2018 - 08/2019

Running my own business.

The activity of my company was based on providing services from car-dealing industry and cleaning useable area.

I was taking care of:

- Business development.
- Marketing & Social Media
- Providing best service for my client's.

## **CERTIFICATES**

- Creating Website part I HTML / CSS / RWD Udemy - 2022
- Creating Website part II SASS / JS / BOOTSTRAP Udemy - 2022
- Creating Websites HTML & CSS & JS for beginners!
  Udemy 2020

## **LANGUAGES**

- English Good knowledge
- German Basic Knowledge

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **High School**

Szkoła Policealna i Ogólnokształcąca - Proffesor · Skoczów

Graduation - 12/2019

# **GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION**

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).